pcwatch.com 2010-12-30

# Windows 7 Tips, Wallpapers, Themes and Software, PCWatch.com

We at PCwatch recognize that privacy is important. We have developed the following privacy policy to protect our customers and inform everyone how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected in relation to your use of our web site located at http://www.pcwatch.com. Your use of PCwatch site and its services indicates your agreement to this privacy policy.

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting your information are to provide you with better services, such as helping you manage your registered user account, if you have one. Here are the types of information we collect.

### 

**◆** Information you provide - We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. For example, when you sign up for an account on our site that requires registration, we may ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). We offer you the choice not to submit such information, but in that case, you might find some web site features will not work properly. Another example is that your posts or comments on our site are considered public information and we may also collect information from them. Thus, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**◆** Automatically Collected Information - Like most web sites, we also use cookies technology to improve the quality of our services. For example, the use of cookies enables us to improve our site by discovering which areas and features are most popular or unpopular, which can help optimize the user experience for you. You can modify your browser's setting to decide whether or not to accept cookies from our site. However, if your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject certain cookies, some portions of our site and its services may not function properly. 

Information from Other Sources - We might receive information about you from other sources, such as your feedback to us via email.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any of your personal information to any third party, except as outlined in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to disclose such information to a third party only if:

### 

**◆** we have your consent; 

**◆** disclosure is required or permitted by law. 

Besides, in the case of business transfers, we may transfer some or all of your information to a third party. Before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy, we will provide notice to you.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### 

◆ We take reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information data. We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

◆ Your account information and access to our services is accessible only through the use of your user name and password. You should protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please note that we will never ask you to disclose your user name or password in an unsolicited phone call or email.

## Third Party Links & Advertisements

### 

◆ PCwatch site contains links to other sites. We have no control over the content of these links; therefore we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

◆ The advertisements on our site are delivered to users by varies advertisers. These third party advertisers may also use cookies technology to collect information, but they will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. PCwatch does not have control over the collection of information for advertising purposes by these advertisers.

## Changes to PCwatch's Privacy Policy

### 

◆ Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time so you are encouraged to check it regularly. The date of the most recent revisions will be identified at the top of this page by its effective date.
